<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SCPFAA Handbook</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/</link><description>Recent content on SCPFAA Handbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discord</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/communication/discord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/communication/discord/</guid><description>Staff have access to the THAUMIEL category. This is not open to the public and should be used when communicating internally.
Important accouncements: #staff-chat, mention, pin General chatter: #staff-chat Off-topic: #other-chat On-topic channels can be created as needed under the THAUMIEL category Quick meetings/ Discord-related meetings can use the staff-vc.
Stages Stages can be useful as a &amp;ldquo;bridge&amp;rdquo; between internal meetings and members (eg. Zoom meeting for members + open Discord stage).</description></item><item><title>Editing</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/handbook/editing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/handbook/editing/</guid><description>TODO: Embed a YT Video detailing instructions</description></item><item><title>Guidelines</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/people/guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/people/guidelines/</guid><description>Keep in mind that anything you do is or could be made public, for example voice/ video recording, chat messages, profile pictures, name/ nickname, etc. You may want to create seprarate account(s) to interact with the SCPFAA podcast/ members.</description></item><item><title>Tools and Tips</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/tools-and-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/tools-and-tips/</guid><description>Google Drive Due to financial reasons, we currently are not part of a Google workspace. This may change in the future, though. For now, we work off of personal Google accounts. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, or you want a separate name/ identity to be associated, please create one.
With regards to storage, if you are concerned about storage quotas, please have me create/ upload the file under the primary account so it won&amp;rsquo;t count against your quota.</description></item><item><title>YouTube</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/communication/youtube/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/communication/youtube/</guid><description>The content determines which channel it should be uploaded to:
The main channel Internal channel Obviously, podcast recordings must go on the main channel, as well as any videos/ livestreams that should be shared with the general audience/ subscribers.
Livestreamed/ recorded meetings can be put on the internal channel as public unless there is a good reason for it to be private. Do not uplaod a video as unlisted.</description></item><item><title>Zoom</title><link>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/communication/zoom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scpaudioarchive.github.io/handbook/communication/zoom/</guid><description>Zoom is used when there limitations on Discord that cannot be overcome (high quality screensharing with audio on Linux, screensharing on iPad, finer meeting security settings, etc.).
We currently have one free account set up (free due to financial constraints). Members can join with their personal zoom accounts.
Tips Keep the meeting link in one place (Google Calendar) instead of Docs, as it can change. If it was changed around the start of the meeting, then it is ok to have it there temporarily.</description></item></channel></rss>